(Penny:)Sorry. Okay, who wants syrup
and who wants cinnamon sugar?
(Sheldon:)-I want oatmeal.
-Yes, well...
(Penny:)...I want a boyfriend whose roommate
isn't a giant pain in the ass.
LEONARD: Ha, ha.
-I'm sure that will happen soon enough.
(Sheldon:)But in the meantime, I still want oatmeal.
You know what? I give up.
He's impossible.
(Sheldon:)I can't be impossible, I exist.
(Sheldon:)I believe what you meant to say is,
"I give up. He's improbable."
Sheldon, you need to find
a better way of dealing with Penny.
What am I supposed to do?
(Sheldon:)Eat French toast on a Monday?
Now, that would be impossible.
I'm saying you can catch more flies
with honey than vinegar.
(Sheldon:)You can catch even more flies
with manure. What's your point?
(Sheldon:)It's a--
[LEONARD SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)Boy, that does smell good.
(Sheldon:)Too bad it's Monday.